Cole, David L. Papers 5588
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Farrenbach Co. vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  2/11/48. Hearing notes re holidays and holiday pay
- Flintkote vs. Textile Workers. Union of America, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  11/14/45. Hearing notes re discharge
- Flying Tiger Line vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  1/3/66. Issue: disability. Hearing notes, correspondence
- Forstmann Wollen Co. vs. Textile Workers Union of American, 1949-1952 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  Hearing notes re layoffs, workload, rates of pay
- Garfield Paper Box vs. unidentified, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  12/24/51. Hearing notes re discharge
- Gates Rubber Co. vs. United Rubber Workers of America, Local 154, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  7/45. (National War Labor Board case) Report and recommendation of Board - re vacation, wage structure, grievance procedure, union security, seniority
- General Dynamics Corp., Electric Boat Division vs. Metal Trades Council of New London County, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 12-13)
  3/31/64. Issue: shift scheduling. Exhibit
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  Cole, Chairman of Board of Inquiry. Hearing notes and correspondence re termination clause, apprenticeships
- GE vs. UE, 1943 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  10/22/43. Issue: production plan
- Gimbel Bros. vs. DPOWA, Dist. 65, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  Hearing notes re rates of pay, promotions & correspondence
- Glass Container Manufacturers Institute Inc. vs. Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  2/26/64. Issue: discharge - safety violations. Hearing notes
- Great Lakes Steel Corp. vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  Hearing notes re grievance handling. Exhibit, correspondence
- Greater NY Brewery Inc. vs. Brewery Workers, Locals 2469 and 345 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  Hearing notes re pension fund
- Hamilton Forms Inc. vs. IBT, Local 1680, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  3/18/49. Hearing notes re back pay awards
- Hawaiian Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 4-5)
  9/1/54. Issues: rates of pay; mileage. Exhibits, hearing notes, correspondence
- Hightstown Rug. Co. vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 200, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  6/1/48. Hearing notes re pay increase - eligibility
- Housatonic Dyeing & Printing Co., Inc. vs. Federation of Dyers, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  4/29/47. Hearing notes re rates of pay
- Idealite Co. vs. UE, Local 448, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  11/50/42. Issue: rate of pay. Hearing notes, correspondence
- Imperial Laundry vs. IBT, Local 37, 1942 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  9/42. Preliminary order to parties
- Ingersoll Rand Co. vs. UE, Local 313, 1949-1951 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  Hearing notes re holiday pay
- ILGWU vs. Brownsville Manufacturing Corp., 1976 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  4/76. Correspondence re contract interpretation
- ILGWU vs. Affiliated Dress Manufacturing. Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  Settled - re holiday fund
- ILGWU vs. Barbizon Corp., 1975 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  Decision of Peter Seitz, designated as arbitrator by Cole re shutdown
- ILGWU vs. Fairfield Noble, Inc., 1971 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  6/l6/75. Issue: discharge ILGWU, Educational Institute of No. Jersey vs. Office & Professional Employees International Union, Local 32, 7/29/71. Issue: discharge
- ILGWU, Educational Institute - Union Health Center vs. OPEIU, Local 32, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  6/72. (Decisions by Sidney Wolff, Tes. as arb. by Cole) re discharge, seniority, suspension
- ILGWU, Educational Institute - Union Health Center vs. OPEIU, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  3/10/66. Issue: fringe benefits. Hearing notes
- ILGWU, Educational Institute - Union Health Center vs. OPEIU, Local 32, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  1/72. Correspondence re discharge, seniority
- ILGWU vs. L'Aiglon Apparel Inc., 1975 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  9/3/75. Issue: Employer contribution to Health, Welfare & Retirement Funds. Hearing notes, exhibit
- ILGWU vs. OPEIU, Local 32, 1970-1973 (Box 79, Folder 11-12)
  Correspondence
- Inland Steel Co.- IAM vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shop Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers & Helpers (IBBISBBFH), 1958 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  6/4/58. Issue: appropriate bargaining unit
- Inland Steel Co. (ISC) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USW) Local 1010, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  11/25/66. Issue: transfers. Exhibits, hearing notes
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), Local 1010, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  6/21/66. Issue: insurance claim
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), Local 1010, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  3/3/67. Issue: safety conditions. Hearing notes
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), Local 1705, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  5/19/67. Issue: relocation allowance. Hearing notes, exhibit
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1967 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  5/22/67. Settled
- Inland Steel Company, Hot Strip Mill vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA, Local 1010, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  9/6/67. Issue: incentive plan. Hearing notes, exhibits
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), Local 1010, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  9/6/67. Issue: disciplinary suspension. Exhibits
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), Local 1010, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  11/28/67. Issue: promotions - upgrading
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1967 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  11/21/67. Issue: discharge - discipline
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1968 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  1/68. Correspondence
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1970 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  2/11/70. Issue: discharge - unsatisfactory performance
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  3/70. Prehearing Briefs and Exhibits re job classification
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1956-1962 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  12/56 - 6/62. Hearing notes re job classification; job evaluation
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1962-1967 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  6/62 - 8/67. Hearing notes re discipline; bargaining unit; job assignment
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1967-1972 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  11/67 - 6/72. Hearing notes re work assignment; job classification
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1973-1976 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  1/73 - 1/76. Hearing notes re discharge; falsification of application; promotion denial
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1945-1946 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  #1-24 (not all Cole's arbitration). Issues: seniority; rates of pay; insubordination; work schedules
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1946-1951 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  #25-49 (not all Cole's). Issues: work classification; hours of work; rates of pay
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1951-1953 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  #58-75 (not all Cole's). Issues: incentives; discharge; rates of pay; job classification
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1953 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  #51-74 (not all Cole's). Issues: promotions; incentive plans; work schedules
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1954 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  #97-ll0 (not all Cole's). Issues: promotions; classification of jobs
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1954-1955 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  #111-131 (not all Cole's). Issues: equipment; equitable incentives
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1955-1956 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  #133-150 (not all Cole's). Issues: discharge, layoffs; job classification; incentive plans
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1957 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  2/57 - 7/57 - #151-179 (Awards of Peter Seitz as well as Cole are contained in boxes 85-86). Issues: incentive plans; work schedules; discipline; job duties
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1952-1957 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  9/52 - 12/57 - #201-224. Issues: overtime; scheduling; job classification
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1957-1958 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  12/57 - 3/58 - #225-250. Issues: incentive plans; job classification
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1958 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  3/58 - 12/58 - #251-274. Issues: promotions; job duties; overtime; grievance filing
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1958-1959 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  8/58 - 1/59 - #275-300. Issues: incentive plans; overtime; seniority; job classification
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1959 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  1/59 - 5/59 - #301-325. Issues: seniority; incentive plans; crew size; discipline
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1959-1960 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  5/59 - 8/60 - #326-351. Issues: job classification; demotion; incentive plans; management rights
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1960-1962 (Box 86, Folder 3-6)
  8/60 - 10/62 - #352-502. Awards other than Cole's - Those of Peter Kelliher)
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1962-1964 (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
  1/62 - 6/64 - #503-570. Awards of Peter Kelliher
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1964-1976 (Box 87, Folder 3-4)
  12/64 - 10/76 - #571-632. Issues: incentive plans; safety; discharge; seniority
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1973-1977 (Box 88, Folder 1-5)
  1973 - 1977. Miscellaneous correspondence, exhibits regarding settled or withdrawn cases
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1966-1976 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  1966 - 1976. Duplicate decisions
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 2-4)
  4/24/70. Issue: demotion; hearing notes; briefs; correspondence
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  7/22/70. Issue: crew size
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1971 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  7/14/71. Issue: discipline; tardiness
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1971 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  10/18/71. Issue: discipline; safety rule violation
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1971 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  7/14/71. Issue: vacation schedules
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  4/17/72. Issue: incentive plan; rates of pay
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  6/8/72. Issue: job classification; rates of pay
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1972 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  6/8/72. Issue: discipline; insubordination
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1972 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1972 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  5/2/72. Issue: discharge; unsatisfactory work
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1972 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  6/30/72. Issue: supplemental unemployment benefit plan
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1973 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  2/7/73. Issue: violation of safety rules
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  4/10/73. Issue: schedules of work
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1973 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  9/5/73. Issue: discharge; fraudulent insurance claim
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  2/6/74. Issue: discharge; falsification of records
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1973 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  11/7/73. Issue: sick benefits
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1974 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  2/6/74. Issue: discipline; absenteeism
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1974 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  7/3/74. Issue: discharge; insubordination
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1974 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  9/13/74. Issue: contract interpretation; grievance process
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1974 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  9/18/74. Issue: discharge; falsification of application
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1974 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  9/18/74. Issue: falsification of application
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1974 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  9/18/74. Issue: discipline; supervisory responsibility
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  4/7/75. Issue: overtime
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  4/21/75. Issue: seniority; work assignment
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  4/2/75. Issue: discipline; discrimination charge
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 95, Folder 2-3)
  8/15/75. Issue: discharge; safety violation
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  8/26/75. Issue: seniority; promotion
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  8/15/75. Issue: discharge; falsification of application
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  12/11/75. Issue: schedules
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  12/11/75. Issue: demotion; physical disability
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1975 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  12/11/75. Issue: discipline; safety rules
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1976 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  1/26/76. Issue: discharge; personal conduct
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1976 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  1/26/76. Issue: discharge; absenteeism
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1976 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  5/26/76. Issue: discharge; personal conduct, overall work record
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1976 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  6/2/76. Issue: reinstatement of disabled employee
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1976 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  10/22/76. Issue: discharge; safety rules
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1976 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  10/22/76. Issue: discharge; unsatisfactory work and insubordination
- Inland Steel Company (ICS) vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1976-1977 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  Issue: appeal of a decision regarding denial of sickness benefits
- Box contains manuals from Inland Steel and Indiana Harbor Works and the folder "New Methods in Grievance Handling" (Box 99.1, Folder All)
  Regarding grievance procedures in International Harvester, Kaiser Steel and others involving the United Steelworkers and the United Auto Workers
- International Harvester vs. United Auto Workers, 1953-1954 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  10/53 - 8/54. Hearing notes regarding many issues: discharge, overtime, transfers, holiday pay to list a few
- International Harvester vs. United Auto Workers, 1954-1957 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  3/54 - 1/57. Hearing notes regarding many issues: discharge, overtime, transfers, holiday pay to list a few
- International Harvester vs. United Auto Workers, 1957-1959 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  1/57 - 6/59. Hearing notes regarding many issues: discharge, overtime, transfers, holiday pay to list a few
- International Harvester vs. United Auto Workers, 1959-1961 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  4/59 - 5/61. Hearing notes regarding many issues: discharge, overtime, transfers, holiday pay to list a few
- International Harvester vs. United Auto Workers, 1954-1961 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  Documentation regarding various cases, contracts, correspondence
- Isle Transportation Corporation vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1947 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  1/17/47. Issue: discharge; transcript; hearing notes
- Johnson and Johnson Company vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 630, 1947 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  8/1/47. Hearing notes regarding rates of pay
- Kaiser Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, District 38, 1960-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3-6)
  Hearing notes regarding rates of pay; minutes of long range planning committee; correspondence; reports
- Isle Transportation Corp., 1947; Text (Box 102.1, Folder 1)
- Johnson & Johnson: Local 630 TWUA, Hearing Notes, Text (Box 102.1, Folder 2)
- Kaiser Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder All)
  Documents regarding long range sharing plan; correspondence; reports; etc.
- Kaiser Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1956-1973 (Box 104, Folder All)
- Kaiser Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  3/63. Minutes and correspondence of long range planning committee
- Kaiser Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  24837
- Kaiser Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1975 (Box 106, Folder All)
- Kaiser Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1975 (Box 107, Folder All)
- Karagheusian, A & M vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 126, 1946-1950 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  Hearing notes regarding incentive system; job displacement
- Lehigh River Mill, Incorporated vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1947-1955 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  Hearing notes regarding union security; discharge
- Lerner Shops vs. Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1957 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  4/57. Issue: rates of pay; hours of work; hearing notes; transcripts; exhibit; briefs
- Lerner Shops vs. Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1947 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
  4/47. Transcript
- Logan, Jonathan Incorporated vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1969-1976 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  Hearing notes regarding sex discrimination; rates of pay
- Logan, Jonathan Incorporated vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  Miscellaneous billing statements
- Logan, Jonathan Incorporated vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1964-1977 (Box 110, Folder 3-8)
  Correspondence, agreements, awards regarding the following issues: insubordination; discharge; holiday pay; seniority; rates of pay, among others
- Logan, Jonathan Incorporated vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1967-1977 (Box 111, Folder 1-13)
  Correspondence, awards, exhibits, etc. Includes decisions by Cole and other arbitrators regarding discharge; holiday pay; rates of pay; work stoppage; job classification
- Los Angeles Examiner vs. Los Angeles Examiner Editorial Association, 1958 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  4/16/58. Issue: rates of pay
- Mack Manufacturing Corporation vs. United Auto Workers, 1948 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  6/8/48. Issue: work assignment outside bargaining unit; transcript
- Mackey Airlines vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  4/14/67. Issue: security; hearing notes; correspondence; etc.
- Macy, R.H. and Company vs. United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, 1947 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  11/1/47. Issue: discharge; incompetence; hearing notes; correspondence; etc.
- Macy, R.H. and Company vs. United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, Local 1-S, 1946-1948 (Box 113, Folder 3-4)
  Awards of Cole and others regarding benefit plans; wages; sick leave; insurance plan; exhibit; hearing notes; correspondence; etc.
- Maidenform Incorporated vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1964-1970 (Box 113, Folder 5-7)
  Issues: rates of pay; elimination of job classification; call-in pay; discharge; correspondence; exhibit
- Major League Baseball Players Association vs. National League of Professional Clubs, 1970 (Box 113.1, Folder 1)
  January 1970. Issue: distribution of World Series Players Fund; transcript; hand written notes
- Mallinckrodt vs. Chemical Workers, 1963 (Box 113.1, Folder 2)
  2/63. Hearing notes regarding plant shutdown
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology vs. unknown, 1968 (Box 113.1, Folder 3)
  4/22/68. Hearing notes regarding ?
- The following case files are under union name (Marine Engineers Beneficial Association - MEBA) rather than company name as per the arrangement by Mr. Cole (Box 114, Folder All)
- The following case files are under union name (Marine Engineers Beneficial Association - MEBA) rather than company name as per the arrangement by Mr. Cole (Box 115, Folder All)
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Keystone Shipping Company, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  6/18/76. Issue: severance pay
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Texas City Tankers Corporation, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  6/18/76. Issue: rates of pay; hearing notes; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Marine Transport Lines, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  4/12/76. Issue: discharge; insubordination; hearing notes; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. United Maritime Corporation, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  12/3/75. Issue: discharge; unsatisfactory performance; hearing notes; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Lykes Brothers Steamship Company, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  12/3/75. Issue: discharge; safety rules; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Amerada Hess Corporation, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  9/24/75. Issue: discharge; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Trinidad Corporation, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  12/17/75. Issue: discharge; insubordination; hearing notes; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Amoco Shipping Company, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  7/9/75. Issue: rates of pay; premium pay; hearing notes; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. United States Lines, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  4/75. Issue: discharge; hearing notes; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. USL, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  7/7/75. Issue: discharge; hearing notes; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Lykes Brothers Steamship Company, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  7/7/75. Issue: rates of pay; hearing notes; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. United Maritime Corporation, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  7/7/75. Issue: discharge; leave of absence; hearing notes; correspondence; exhibit
- MEBA vs. National Bulk Carriers, 1975-1976 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  Correspondence regarding meeting of Licensed Personnel Board of which Cole was a member
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Prudential Lines, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  3/19/75. Issue: discrimination; hearing notes; correspondence; exhibit